<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="desc_ab_1">This monster may ignore enemy figures and the effects of terrain while moving. It must end its movement in an empty space following normal movement rules.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_2">If this attack deals at least 1 :dam: (after the defense roll), the target is stunned. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_3">This attack ignores X :def: rolled on the defense dice. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_4">Add X additional damage to the attack.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_5">Add X additional damage to the attack.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_6">Choose a hero adjacent to this monster. That hero must test :mig:. If he fails, roll 1 yellow power die. The hero suffers 1 :fat: per :dam: rolled, and this monster recovers 1 :dam: per Fatigue suffered. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_7">If this attack deals at least 1 :dam: (after the defense roll), the target is Poisoned. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_8">Each hero adjacent to this monster must test Awareness. Each hero that fails is Immobilized.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_9">This monster may move through spaces containing heroes.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_10">Add X additional spaces to the range.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_11">Each hero within 3 spaces of this monster must test :wil:. Each hero that fails suffers 1 :fat:.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_12">If attacked by any non-adjacent hero, this monster may add 1 brown die to its defense roll.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_13">When this monster attacks, it uses the dice of a figure (overlord\'s choice) in its line of sight. If a hero is chosen, the overlord may choose which of the hero\'s equipped weapon to use. The monster cannot use any of the figure\'s other abilities, just the dice.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_14">After making an attack roll, this monster may convert up to X range to :dam:, or up to X :dam: to range.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_15">The target suffers 1 :fat:.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_16">Each time a hero enters a space adjacent to this monster, that hero suffers X :dam:.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_17">This attack affects all figures adjacent to the target space.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_18">Choose a hero adjacent to this monster. That hero must test :wil:. If he fails, he moves 2 spaces dircectly away from this monster and is Immobilized.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_19">A hero adjacent to this monster that declares an attack must spend 1 :sur: or the attack is considered a miss.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_20">Starting with the target space, trace a path of 4 spaces in any direction. All figures on this path are affected by this attack. Each figure rolls defense dice separately. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_21">Each hero adjacent to this monster must test :wil:. Each hero that fails suffers 2 :fat:.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_22">Perform an attack targeting all figures adjacent to this monster. Each figure rolls defense dice separately.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_23">Each hero adjacent to this monster must test :awa:. Each hero that fails is Immobilized.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_24">Until the start of your next turn, this monster can only be affected by attacks from adjacent figures.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_25">Each hero adjacent to this monster must suffer 1 :fat: to move out of his current space; this is in addition to any other :fat: suffered to move. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_26">This monster cannot spend surges on abilities unless it is within 3 spaces of any master monster or a lieutenant.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_27">Each attack that targets this monster must roll 3 additional range beyond the normally required amount or the attack is a miss.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_28">When this monster is defeated, remove it from the map and then replace it with a minion of the same type, ignoring group limits.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_29">This monster may attack targets up to 2 spaces away. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_30">Choose a hero adjacent to this monster. That hero must test :mig:. If he fails, remove the hero from the map, then place him on any empty space within 3 spaces of his original space. He counts as entering that space. Then the hero suffers 1 :dam:. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_31">If this attack deals at least 1 :dam: (after the defense roll), the target is Diseased. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_32">Perform an attack. This attack affects each figure within range of this monder\'s attack. Each figure rolls defense die separately.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_33">This monster is immune to Pierce and to all conditions.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_34">This monster may choose to ignore any game effect that would force it to move.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_35">Choose a minion within 3 spaces of this monster. Place that minion in an empty space adjacent to this monster.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_36">Both of this monster\'s actions on a turn may be attack actions.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_37">Each minion within 3 spaces of this monster may reroll 1 die on each of its attacks. Each minion may only benefit from one monster with Command at a time.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_38">This monster deals +1 :dam: for each other monster adjacent to the target.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_39">When this monster is defeated, replace it with 2 minions of the same type in the closest available empty spaces, ignoring group limits.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_40">If this attack deals at least 1 :dam: (after the defense roll), the target is Immobilized.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_41">When attacking, this monster may target 2 separate heroes. This monster makes 1 attack roll and each hero rolls defense dice separately.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_42">This monster recovers X :dam:.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_43">Choose a monster within 3 spaces of this monster and roll 1 red power die. The chosen monster recovers :dam: equal to the :dam: rolled.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_44">Choose a hero adjacent to this monster. The hero must test :mig:. If the hero fails, he is Immobilized. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_45">Remove the target from the map, then place him on any empty space within 3 spaces of his original space. He counts as entering that space.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_46">Each hero within 3 spaces of this monster must test :wil:.  Each hero that fails suffers 1 :fat:.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_47">Each time a hero enters a space adjacent to this monster, that hero suffers 1 :fat:.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_48">If a hero is defeated by this monster, remove his hero token from the map and place it on this monster’s base. The hero cannot be revived until this monster is defeated, at which point his hero token is placed in one of this monster’s spaces.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_49">This monster may move its Speed, ignoring enemy figures as it does so. When it finishes its movement, perform a single attack that targets each figure this monster moved through. Each figure rolls defense dice separately. Limit once per turn.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_50">Choose an adjacent hero. That hero must test :awa:. If he fails, he suffers 3 :dam:.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_51">This monster may not perform more than 1 move action during a single turn.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_52">This monster ignores all effects of lava. Each time this monster ends its turn in a space containing lava, it recovers 1 :dam:. In addition, this monster never suffers :dam: from Burning. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_53">If this attack deals at least 1 :dam: (after the defense roll), the target is Burning. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_54">When this monster is defeated, each hero adjacent to this monster suffers 1 :dam:. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_55">Each of this monster\'s attacks targeting a hero with 2 or less :mig: gains +1 :dam:. </string>
    <string name="desc_ab_56">Move each adjacent Cursed hero up to 2 spaces in any direction of your choice.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_57">If this attack deals at least 1 :dam: (after the defense roll), the target is Cursed.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_58">This monster may move 3 spaces, then perform an attack.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_59">When a hero adjacent to this monster would discard a Poisoned or Diseased Condition card, he instead keeps the card.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_60">Perform an attack targeting up to 2 heroes adjacent to this monster. 1 attack roll is made but each hero rolls defense dice separately. Each target that suffers at least 1 :dam: from this attack (after the defense roll) is Immobilized.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_61">When this monster is defeated, each adjacent hero must test :wil:. Each hero that fails is Cursed.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_62">Each hero adjacent to this monster at the start of his turn must test :wil:. Each hero that fails is Diseased.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_63">Remove this figure from the map and place it in empty or occupied spaces up to 3 spaces away. Each figure occupying any target space is moved to the closes empty space of your choice and suffers 1 :fat:. Limit once per monster turn.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_64">Each minion monster from this monster group within 5 spaces of this monster may immediately move 2 spaces.</string>
    <string name="desc_ab_65">If this attack deals at least 1 :dam: (after defense roll), the target is Weakened.</string>
</resources>
